Now again you're aware of your posture, you realize that your shoulders are rounded and that you need to do something about it, I got something very simple for you to do.
This is a Shoulder Elevation and Depression With Arms Overhead.
Now I have to warn you that if you have a little bit of difficulty with this move, please refer to the Shoulder Elevation and Depression either with the hands by the side, or the hands in front, the arms in front before you temp this if it's a little bit challenging for you.
But basically what this looks like is, once you're sitting on your ball, the sit bones, you're bringing your arms overhead, you're going to shrug your shoulders towards your ears with that inhalation, and then as you exhale, you're going to press down.
And if you notice, I'm not bending my elbows.
It's not about this, it's about the shoulder moves.
So feel like your shoulder blades is sliding up the back as you inhale and sliding down the back as you exhale.
And you really going to make sure that you're pressing down with the shoulder blades, with the back muscles into your hips, or towards your hips, rather.
So inhale, exhale.
Again, this may not be the easiest thing to do if you're trying it for the first time, so refer to the clips with the hands by the side or the hands in front of you, so you can get your body used to doing this at first, and then once you master those, then you'll feel free to do this.
I guarantee you, your shoulders will feel better.
At first, it might be a little sore, but they'll feel better and they'll look better.